<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[ICO Mafia]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[ICO Mafia]]></description>
        <link>http://icomafia.org/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 03:01:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://icomafia.org/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 03:01:21 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Contracts Might Not Be as Smart as You Think]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Smart Contracts Might Not Be as Smart as You Think</h1><p>Smart contracts are supposed to be just that: smart. However, some smart contracts currently circulating aren&apos;t quite making the grade - with vulnerabilities exposing millions of dollars worth of Ethereum to potential theft. Smart contracts are computer protocols meant to digitally facilitate, verify, or enforce the execution of contracts.</p><img src="http://bitcoinist.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/as-ethereum-dollar.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bitcoinist.com/smart-contracts-might-not-smart-think/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">39cd193e-6c65-428f-9198-17cbf70a542f</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 03:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Currency and Blockchain: How are Financial Institutions Responding?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Digital Currency and Blockchain: How are Financial Institutions Responding?</h1><p>Perhaps the industry most obviously threatened by blockchain is banking and financial services. Digital currencies and blockchain platforms are by nature in the business of putting financial overlords out of business. If individuals and institutions can transact directly at a significantly lower cost due to the removal of exchange middlemen, then there is less of a need for traditional banks and other controllers of the money game.</p><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/1*oWw1LbUgewXGY5uLrpI80A.jpeg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://shift.newco.co/digital-currency-and-blockchain-how-are-financial-institutions-responding-71091b2772c3</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8bdba12f-de7a-44b6-9a90-d6af14d56fd9</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 19:40:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coinbase is erratically overcharging some users and emptying their bank accounts]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Coinbase is erratically overcharging some users and emptying their bank accounts</h1><p>A growing number of Coinbase customers are complaining that the cryptocurrency exchange withdrew unauthorized money out of their accounts. In some cases, this drained their linked bank accounts below zero, resulting in overdraft charges. In a typical anecdote posted on Reddit, one user said they purchased Bitcoin, Ether, and Litecoin for a total of $300 on February 9th.</p><img src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/58709295/846660080.jpg.0.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.theverge.com/2018/2/15/17017374/coinbase-cryptocurrency-bitcoin-ether-unauthorized-charges</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1d61bac2-3f3c-479b-88ff-52e4f27ae775</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 14:35:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hicky | Blockchain Dating ICO]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Hicky | Blockchain Dating ICO</h1><p>Hicky is a decentralized dating app (DApp) and can be thought of as tinder on the Blockchain. We are using our Token economy as well as the power of the blockchain to ensure trust on our platform and thus optimize dating results.</p><img src="https://143245-414241-1-raikfcquaxqncofqfm.stackpathdns.com/assets/img/team/dusia-lewandowska.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://hicky.io/#why-hicky</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c985cd5a-f2e7-4171-bd5b-41328add0609</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 14:35:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ex-PayPal executive David Sacks explains how his new company will change crypto trading]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ex-PayPal executive David Sacks explains how his new company will change crypto trading</h1><p>I interviewed David Sacks last August about his interest in cryptocurrency. His interest was well-founded as the whole asset class took off last fall. In a recent report by Axios, Sacks said he&apos;s raised a new venture fund with partner and well-known Silicon Valley angel investor Bill Lee.</p><img src="https://fm.cnbc.com/applications/cnbc.com/resources/img/editorial/2017/08/14/104652209-sacks-handout.1910x1000.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/02/06/ex-paypal-david-sacks-on-craft-fund-and-harbor.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ad0cae55-1ff8-44c6-ac6d-004202abfc74</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 14:35:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum, Bitcoin Cash, Ripple, Stellar, Litecoin, NEM, NEO, EOS: Price Analysis, February 2, 2018]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bitcoin, Ethereum, Bitcoin Cash, Ripple, Stellar, Litecoin, NEM, NEO, EOS: Price Analysis, February 2, 2018</h1><p>There are various reasons behind the panic currently gripping the crypto world - increased regulations, hacking, and crackdown by various governments. Additionally, the last leg of the rally looked frothy as traders gobbled up cryptocurrencies at crazy levels out of fear of missing out on the rally.</p><img src="https://cointelegraph.com/storage/uploads/view/8d3a81f02185989511bd0ed8e768cc0c.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ethereum-bitcoin-cash-ripple-stellar-litecoin-nem-neo-eos-price-analysis-february-2-2018</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">30423861-95da-4827-a034-9969b6649041</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 14:35:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin: Africa's first exchange aims for 1 billion users]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bitcoin: Africa&apos;s first exchange aims for 1 billion users</h1><p>Luno, founded in South Africa in 2013, has plans to become one of the leading cryptocurrency traders in the world. CEO and founder Marcus Swanepoel has a goal that would leave many bigger companies in the shade: 1 billion customers by 2025.</p><img src="http://i2.cdn.turner.com/money/dam/assets/180126133327-africa-bitcoin-780x439.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://money.cnn.com/2018/02/14/technology/bitcoin-luno-billion-users</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8afb2da2-3eea-4e9a-9bd4-ab233691b4a5</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 14:35:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Western Union Confirms XRP Integration of Ripple Blockchain Trial]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Western Union Confirms XRP Integration of Ripple Blockchain Trial</h1><p>Get Trading Recommendations and Read Analysis on Hacked.com for just $39 per month. Western Union has formally confirmed that its Ripple-based blockchain trial will include XRP integration, making the money transfer giant the largest firm to test XRP in its internal payment flows. As CCN reported, Western Union confirmed rumors about the partnership on Wednesday.</p><img src="https://www.ccn.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Western-Union-NY.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.ccn.com/western-union-confirms-ripple-blockchain-trial-will-feature-xrp-integration/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b5a6a598-de16-4976-af9f-bda6457ba64d</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 14:35:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Japan Cracks Down on Foreign ICO Agency Operating Without License - Bitcoin News]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Japan Cracks Down on Foreign ICO Agency Operating Without License - Bitcoin News</h1><p>The Japanese financial regulator will be issuing its first warning since the legalization of cryptocurrencies as a method of payment in Japan. An overseas initial coin offering agency has reportedly been attracting Japanese investors without a license, repeatedly ignoring the agency&apos;s advice to cease operating in the country.</p><img src="https://news.bitcoin.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/FSA-warning-banner1.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://news.bitcoin.com/japan-cracks-foreign-ico-agency-operating-without-license/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">684921f5-b291-4de1-9904-9078a7fad14d</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 14:35:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Nano Vision Might Be The Most Important Crypto Company For Mankind]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Why Nano Vision Might Be The Most Important Crypto Company For Mankind</h1><p>Richard K. Yu with Studypool recently brought up some salient, if somewhat deflating points for the crypto world. First, much of blockchain&apos;s meteoric rise-bitcoin&apos;s price climbing to $20,000, 235 ICOs debuting in 2017-has the characteristics of a market bubble. A bubble eventually pops, which means that many of today&apos;s hot new blockchain products will be fail.</p><img src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/influencive.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/31135619/unnamed1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.influencive.com/nano-vision-might-important-crypto-company-mankind/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3a6eeac3-0a45-492f-b309-b94ae0177e5b</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 14:35:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>